hey what's up Ruben Kong here of Jin Boy
TV have you ever had an idea or a dream
or a career that you've always wanted to
pursue well now you can start 2017 with
a new career what's stopping you start
now with manual life start now 60
seconds pitch pitches your idea dream or
new adventure and you can win 10,000
ring to get your new idea kick started
with manual life start now and here is
how you participate step one record a
60- seconds video of yourself sharing
with us your idea step two upload that
video on your Instagram account and #
maniz start now the best tree ideas will
win 10,000 ring and get that idea
kickstarted for more information log on
to Manu lifestart now.com domm good
luck